{
    "id": "ef0e23da8ea14a13bee0f75e6cdf268e",
    "title": "Comparison Of Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is …………………….. than me.",
            "description": "Use a comparative expression before than.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "taller",
                "tallest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………………. specimen we have.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the fine",
                "the finer",
                "the finest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The job was ……………………….. than I thought.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "difficult",
                "more difficult",
                "most difficult"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A mango is as …………………………. as an apple.",
            "description": "Use the positive form of the adjective in the structure as...as....",
            "answers": [
                "nutritious",
                "more nutritious",
                "most nutritious"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Curd is …………………….. than milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "healthy",
                "more healthy",
                "healthier"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ……………………. friends than me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ………………….. than that.",
            "description": "Use the comparative form before than.",
            "answers": [
                "expensive",
                "more expensive",
                "most expensive"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A tablet is not as …………………………. as a computer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "useful",
                "more useful",
                "usefuller"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………………….. than I thought.",
            "description": "Prettier is the comparative form of pretty. ",
            "answers": [
                "pretty",
                "prettier",
                "more pretty"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the ……………………… girl I have ever met.",
            "description": "Prettiest is the superlative form of pretty.",
            "answers": [
                "most pretty",
                "prettiest",
                "most prettiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You are taking ………………………… than you should.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "long",
                "more long",
                "longer"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the ………………………. meal I ever had.",
            "description": "Tastiest is the superlative form of tasty. ",
            "answers": [
                "most tasty",
                "tastier",
                "tastiest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}